phonicarecords.com 2015-06-16

# Vinyl Records Specialists, London Soho Vinyl Music Records - Phonica Records - Latest Releases, Pre-Orders and Merchandise

## 

latest release

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

sale

coming  
soon

pre  
order

## 

### 

Format: 

Availability: 

| 

## was £

### inc VAT  
  
---|---  
  
### review

  * Account Details
  * Orders History
  * My Wishlist
  * Address Book
  * Help

### Account Details

In this section you can change the look & feel of our website according to your preferences.

The styles you set up will be assigned to your account and preserved. When you log out, the website will return to default settings.

Username:|   
---|---  
First Name:|   
Last Name:|   
Email:|   
  
Logged in with: 

### Orders History

In this section you can review orders you have placed under this account. If you order has been completed, you will be able to download an invoice for it in PDF format by clicking the corresponding link. You will need to have PDF reader application installed on your computer such as [Adobe Acrobat Reader](http://get.adobe.com/uk/reader/) in order to view it.

Order ID | Status | Order Date | TOTAL | Invoice  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
### My Wishlist

This section displays your current wishlist.

Product Cover | Product Name | Availability | Action  
---|---|---|---  
  
### Address Book

For faster checkout, use your personal Address Book to save addresses to which your orders may be shipped or billed.

To create a new Address Book entry, enter the information requested by the form below, then click Save. To edit an entry, click the Edit button, make any changes to the entry, then click Save. To delete an entry, click Delete.

Address Name | Date | Actions  
---|---|---  
  
### View address from Addressbook

Address Field | Value  
---|---  
Address ID|   
Date Modified|   
  
Address Field | Value  
---|---  
Address Title|   
First Name|   
Middle Name|   
Last Name|   
Company|   
Country|   
Address Line 1|   
Address Line 2|   
City|   
State|   
Postcode|   
Phone|   
FAX|   

### Add Address Book

Please fill in the form below to add address to your personal address book. Please note that the fields marked with asterisk ( * ) are mandatory.

### Edit Address Book

Please fill in the form below to edit address from your personal address book. Please note that the fields marked with asterisk ( * ) are mandatory.

### Delete address from Addressbook

Are you sure you want to delete this address?

### Help

We're more than happy to have a friendly chat with you about any problems or queries you may have, record related or otherwise.

You can contact Phonica Records via email at [customerservice@phonicarecords.com](mailto:customerservice@phonicarecords.com) or by telephone on 02070256071 between 11:30 and 19:30 Monday to Saturday.

### Quick Links

For faster checkout, use your personal Address Book to save addresses to which your orders may be shipped or billed.

To create a new Address Book entry, enter the information requested by the form below, then click Save. To edit an entry, click the Edit button, make any changes to the entry, then click Save. To delete an entry, click Delete.

### Questions we get asked, frequently.

Before reaching for the phone we do ask that you have a quick read through the following, just in case we can save you the keystrokes or the cost of a phone call.

#### Where are my records?

We aim to dispatch the same day if orders are placed before 4pm Monday to Friday so anytime after this we can usually say that they are “on their way”. Depending on which delivery service you choose we may be able to track your records, please see shipping methods below.

#### Its been ages, I think my records are lost in the post – what now?

Sometimes packages do go missing. We have to allow a certain period of time for us to be able to consider items lost.

UK – 15 working days.  
Overseas – 28 working days.

While these may seem excessive, we have known items to take this long and it is only after these periods have elapsed that we can claim for compensation.

#### Do you have a particular record in stock?

If you are able to add a record to your basket on the website then it is almost definitely in stock. Our website stock is shared with our physical shop and is updated constantly. However, sometimes things go missing or are sold in the shop at the same time as on our website. If we are unable to completely fulfil your order we will contact to let you know whether we might be able to source another copy of the record or whether we will have to adjust your order and payment.

Dear customer, due to a recent security upgrade imposed by our online payment providers our checkout page will only work with the latest versions of all main browsers. This has been done to ensure your details remain secure while shopping on our site. If you have trouble connecting please upgrade to the latest version of your favourite browser and that should resolve the issue. If the problem persists please get in touch with our customer service team - customerservice@phonicarecords.com - thanks. 

## Your Basket

Product | Type | Qty | Unit Price | Total  
---|---|---|---|---  
You haven't added any products to your basket yet.  

Free Shipping Hint   
---  
  
You will be entitled to free shipping  
if you spend another £50 (including VAT!) - UK customers only. You are entitled to "Free Shipping"! - UK customers only.  

You might also be interested in ...   
---  
  
buy

buy

buy

buy

buy  

Totals  
---  
Product Total | £0.00  
Order Total | £0.00  
0  
Total does not include shipping or VAT (sales tax) charges  
  
Free Shipping  
---  
Our normal shipping is FREE to the Mainland UK if you spend at least £50 including VAT on goods.  

## Login

To access your account, enter your e-mail address and password below.

Don't have an account yet? [Create one](http://www.phonicarecords.com/user/register)!

If you don't remember your password, click [Forgot your Password?](http://www.phonicarecords.com/user/password) to have your new password emailed to you.   
Please remember that password is case-sensitive.

Phonica Records now also supports Facebook and Twitter logins. If you have an account with one of those social services, you can use it to log in to our website. Please click one of the corresponding buttons below in order to do that.

## Register

Sign up for an account today and benefit from faster checkout and more site features.  
Note that passwords must be at least between four (4) to ten (10) characters long.

Already have an account? [Login](http://www.phonicarecords.com/user/login)!

If you don't remember your password, click [Forgot your Password](http://www.phonicarecords.com/user/password)? to have your new password emailed to you.

## Password Recovery

Enter the e-mail address associated with your account. Click submit to have your new password e-mailed to you.

If you don't remember your email address, but know other details about your account we can try to find it out for you. Please contact customerservice@phonicarecords.com.

## search results

You have searched for:  Unfortunately, we couldn't find it.

Use the form below to perform an advanced search of our database.

## Privacy Policy

Who we are

In this Privacy Policy references to 'we' and 'us' are to Phonica Records.

What information we collect and how

The information we collect via this website may include:

(1) Any personal details you type in and submit, such as name, address, email address, etc.  
(2) Your IP address (this is your computer's individual identification number) which is automatically logged by our web server. This is used to note your interest in our website.  
(3) Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers).  
(4) Session information stored in cookies, these do not include any personal information and are used to ensure the correct data is extracted from the database when using our interactive systems.  
(5) Under no circumstances will we hold sensitive payment details such as your card number, expiry date and security code. All transactions are handled using a secure server hosted by Paypal and Barclays EPDQ located at http://www.paypal.com and http://www.barclaycard.co.uk/business accordingly.

What we do with your information

Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. The details we collect will be used:-

(1) To process your order, to provide after-sales service (we may pass your details to another organisation to supply/deliver products or services you have purchased and/or to provide after-sales service);  
(2) To comply with legal requirements.  
(3) In certain cases we may use your email address to send you information on our other products and services. In such a case you will be offered the option to opt in/out before completing your purchase.

We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use our site and issuing our e-mails for us. Rest assured that third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

Your rights

(1) You can ask us to update or remove your personal information by emailing customerservice@phonicarecords.com or by writing to us at our customer services address in (2) below. However, please note that we may need to keep some personal data in order to process orders or to comply with customer service or after sale obligations.  
(2) You also have the right to request a copy of any personal information we hold about you. To do this, simply write to us at the following address, enclosing a cheque for £10 payable to Vinyl Factory Publishing Ltd to cover our administration costs:-

Customer Services (Data Subject Request)  
Phonica Records  
51 Poland Street  
London W1F 7BE

Other Websites

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.

## Sign Up to Phonica Records Newsletter
